# Rebecca Jensen

Seattle, WA

425.281.2754 - jensenrs@gmail.com

I'm a UX/UI Designer who has tackled the full scope of projects, from the initial ideation to ongoing iteration. I can hold the macro aspects of user experience in one hand, while drilling down the details in the other. I enjoy thinking out loud, considering other perspectives, and teasing out solutions.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

UX/UI Designer, motion.social, Seattle, WA

Jul. 2015 - Present

Motion.social is an online tool for organizing group fitness activities.

Responsible for designing the entire product, from ideation to iteration

- Interviewed target users
  - Identified planning as a common goal and pain point
  - Created user personas to maintain design focus
- Developed the product
  - Translated larger concepts into concrete features
  - Outlined user flow and site map
- · Designed the visuals
  - Developed branding voice and style to fit our social fitness focus
  - Designed user interface, considering responsive displays and best practices
- Iterated
  - Followed up with users to identify areas of improvement
  - Used quick prototypes to test ideas
- Directed
  - Proposed new features and next steps, prioritizing for impact on the user
- Adjusted
  - Self-directed work, managing multiple design threads

UX/UI Designer (volunteer), Cascade Orienteering Club, Seattle, WA

Dec. 2014 - Present

Cascade Orienteering Club is a non-profit organization for orienteering events and education.

Completed website overhaul using the UX process

- Surveyed and interviewed a variety of users, identified goals and frustrations
- Created user personas
- Outlined user flows and site map
- Wireframed and prototyped design solutions
- Designed user interface
- Wrote Wordpress theme (PHP) from scratch
- Launched a user-oriented, responsive Wordpress site

Marketing Manager, Meridian Geographics (MerGeo), Seattle, WA

MerGeo produces running and navigation events year-round in Washington State.

- Rebranded MerGeo through logo and website redesign
- Surveyed event participants, analyzed feedback to identify ways to improve user experience
- Analyzed web traffic, registration, e-newsletter, and social media data
- Designed promotional print and web graphics
- Wrote website content, newsletters, press releases
- Filmed and edited promotional videos

Dec. 2012 - May 2015

Sales Manager, Gregg's Bellevue Cycles, Bellevue, WA

• Managed staff of 20+ employees

2011 - 2013

Sales Person, Gregg's Bellevue Cycles, Bellevue, WA

• Top 2 salesperson during summer sales competition

2009 - 2011

# **EDUCATION**

BLOC, UX Design, 2014 - 2015

Whitman College, Studio Art Major, 2003 - 2007

## REFERENCES

Justin Huff, Co-Founder & CTO, motion.social 206.295.1950 - jjhuff@motion.social

David Longdon, Co-Founder & President, motion.social 541.514.1502 - david.longdon@motion.social

Eric Bone, Owner, Meridian Geographics 206.291.8250 - eric@mergeo.com

## **SOFTWARE & LANGUAGES**

Design	UX	Code	Languages	Video	Other
Sketch	UXPin	Bootstrap	HTML5 / CSS3	iMovie	American Sign Language
Photoshop	InVision	Wordpress	PHP	FinalCut	Map and compass
Illustrator	Omnigraffle	Sublime Text	jQuery		
	Google Forms	MAMP			
		CyberDuck			